

Fernando Falci Senior Developer print@falci.me

#### **Information**

Location Barcelona

Experience 10+ years

Availabilty 1 month

Relocation Amsterdam area

#### **Skills**

HTML/CSS

JS/TS

React

NodeJS

GraphQL

#### **About me**

I'm a passionate developer and have been working on web development in the last decade.

I have a graduate (and post-graduate) background and have experience with most actual technologies such React, NodeJS, and Module Federation, working for one of the biggest company from Europe.

With strong soft skills, I have achieved great results as a team leader, applying agile techniques such as scrum, code review, and TDD.

# **Experience**



## **Senior Frontend Developer**

Adevinta O Spain

Feb 2020 - Present

With many websites accross the world, Adevinta is one of the biggest companies focused on dedicated marketplaces. I work on the frontend of the company's backoffice, mainly in React (Typescript) and Rest/GraphQL. I also work on the backend, mainly in NodeJS. Here I had the opportunity to work with Module Federation and MonoRepo to make the company's codebase more modular and reusable.



#### **Javascript Developer**

eDreams Odigeo Spain

Jun 2017 - Feb 2020

eDreams is a travel agency focused on the travel industry. I worked on the frontend of the company's website, mainly in Backbone, transitioning to React. Strong attention to details when following the UX desigers' mock-us. I also gained a lot of knowledge related to A/B testing.



### **Development Analyst**

Mobile-DI Remote

( ) 2015 - Mar 2018

Mobile-DI is a software company that provides software development services to enterprises and governments. I worked as an analyst at Mobile-DI, where I designed and help to implement the solution for each client. I also lead a team of frontend developers, remotely. I worked on a variety of projects, most of them Angular and AngularJS.



H Nov 2014 - Jun 2017

MATERA Systems is a software company that provides software development services for the banking sector. I worked mainly in a remote team, where I code the frontend following the mock-ups profided by the UX designers.

#### **Education**



## **Object Oriented Development in Java**

UniCesumar Brazil

2012 - 2013\*



# **Analysis and Software Development**

UNIPAR O Brazil

2007 - 2009



@falci

in fernandofalci

/falci

# Fernando Falci

Senior Developer print@falci.me